{
    "subject": "resource/Stockdale_High_School_(Bakersfield,_California)",
    "predicate": "property/mascot",
    "object": "Mustangs",
    "human_readable": "The mascot of Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California) is Mustangs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8978831768035889,
            "question": "What is the mascot of Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8170166611671448,
            "question": "What animal represents Stockdale High School's mascot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7751736044883728,
            "question": "In which state is Stockdale High School situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7391592860221863,
            "question": "Where is Stockdale High School located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3776308298110962,
            "question": "Are there any other schools with a similar mascot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26114004850387573,
            "question": "How do mascots contribute to school events and traditions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2245337963104248,
            "question": "What are some possible symbols associated with Mustangs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1965893805027008,
            "question": "What can you infer about the school spirit based on its mascot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13392987847328186,
            "question": "How might the mascot influence students' sense of identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.027430541813373566,
            "question": "Can you think of any famous figures associated with horses?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The mascot of Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California) is Mustangs.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2457_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the mascot influence students' sense of identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2457_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you infer about the school spirit based on its mascot?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2457_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some possible symbols associated with Mustangs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2457_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2457_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the athletic teams at Stockdale High School are known as the Stockdale Mustangs. Therefore, the statement that the mascot of Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California) is Mustangs is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}